( Children 's voices )
One , two , three , knock on the wall !
One , two , three , knock on the ...
( Laughter )
Run ! I 'm going to catch you !
( Children shouting )
( Telephone ringing )
Good Shepherd orphanage . Hello ?
It 's all ready .
She 's playing . We haven 't told her yet .
Laura will be very happy in her new home . Don 't worry .
See you in the afternoon .
Your friends will miss you a lot , Laura .
Got you !
The orphanage
Boy : mommy !
Mommy !
I 'll go , it 's my turn .
Boy : mommy !
I 'm coming !
Woman : sim n !
They 're outside . Listen .
Come on , go to sleep .
Sim n , darling .
Oh , I see !
Watson and pepe have been playing until very late ...
And now they can 't get in , right ?
Come on , in you go .
Aren 't you a bit old for this ?
Weren 't you scared here , when you were little ?
No , darling . You couldn 't be afraid .
There was a gang of us ...
And the lighthouse was on all night .
Lighthouse ? It 's still there ...
But it doesn 't work anymore .
I 'll show you tomorrow when we go to the beach .
Why doesn 't it work ?
Can you keep a secret ?
Actually , it does work .
But the light 's invisible , and it protects us from danger .
Invisible light ?
Ok , try this .
Look at the window , you 'll see .
Over there . Don 't move .
Can you see it ?
( Sim n laughs )
What ? Did you see it ?
Those kids that are coming ...
Why can 't they stay at home ?
Darling , because they 're special children ...
And they need a lot of special care .
They can 't come and go , because they 're too far away .
Do you understand ?
Can I sleep with you tonight ?
( Inhales deeply )
You 're pushing it !
( Indistinct chatter )
( Hammering , piano playing in the distance )
( Playing slow tune )
( Tune continues )
Dad , are you not coming to the beach ?
Aren 't Watson and pepe going ?
No , they didn 't sleep a wink last night .
You 're such a smart-ass ! You have friends only when it suits .
Ok , wise guy , take your pill .
( Music stops )
( Hammering , drill whirring )
" S " for sim n ! Mm .
Go upstairs and get your bag .
Dad will meet us there later , ok ?
Laura : hmm ?
One of us should talk to sim n .
About his invisible friends .
It 's normal , don 't worry . He 's lonely , he 's bored .
He 'll forget them as soon as the real kids arrive .
( Thumping )
( Shouting )
Man : calm down ! man 2 : ok .
Everything will work out .
We 'll have a great home .
I 'm so glad we 're here together .
( Sighs )
( Tune continues )
Sim n : pirate . Laura : pirate .
Cave . Cave .
And lighthouse . And lighthouse .
Let 's see .
Once upon a time , there was a very , very bad pirate ...
Who hid his treasures in a cave , near a lighthouse .
And what treasures ? Stolen treasures .
But it wasn 't easy ... But
to get into the cave .
Laura : they 'd click a stone ... sim n : and how did they get in ?
Laura : in a gap in the rocks
that big stone inside the other stone
and the rock did ... Like this .
And there 's where they used to hide all of their treasures .
( Waves echoing )
( Indistinct talking )
( Water trickling )
Hello ?
Sim n ?
( Yells ) sim n , let 's go !
( Whispers ) what 's your name ?
I 'm sim n . Do you want to play ?
Why ? Can 't you play ?
Do you want to come to my house to play later ?
Sim n ...
What are you doing there ?
We are playing .
But Watson and pepe weren 't going to come .
It 's not them , it 's another boy .
Then tell him to play somewhere else . It 's dangerous here .
Come on , let 's go .
Can he come home to play ?
( Affirmative grunt )
Carlos : why are you dropping shells , sim n ?
Sim n : it 's a path for my friend to follow ...
So he can come home and play .
Laura : he made a new friend . How 's that ?
Carlos : another one ?
We won 't have room for all these kids .
( Thunder rumbling )
( Thunder crashing )
( Car approaching )
( Knocking )
Hello . Good afternoon .
Sorry I didn 't call , but I couldn 't get your number .
I 'm benigna escobedo .
I 'm a social worker .
I 'm sorry you 've come so far ...
But I hadn 't arranged any interviews for today .
Interviews ? No , I 'm here for sim n .
What a sitting room !
It 's a beautiful house .
How did you find it ?
I grew up here . It was an orphanage .
I always wanted to return , so we thought of the home .
Home ?
For special children . That 's not why you came ?
You 'll need a lot of people for that .
It 's not that kind of a home .
We 'll be happy with five or six children .
More would be too complicated , right ?
What about sim n ?
Yes , yes . Of course .
I received his file yesterday ...
And thought , " I should visit them "
" in case they need anything . "
( Thunder )
Will you make many changes in the house ?
Sorry , but I don 't understand why you 're here .
( Bells chiming )
This information is old .
I know , but I received it all .
There are new treatments , an experimental program ...
That requires an application ,
and I thought you might be interested .
As you might know , my husband is a doctor .
We 're aware of all treatments for sim n 's disease .
Now please leave .
Sim n doesn 't know he 's adopted , or about his illness ...
And I like to deal with these issues
when my husband is at home .
( Door slams )
Change of address
HIV positive
( thunder rumbling )
( Faint banging )
( Faint clinking , banging )
( Clinking continues )
Carlos .
I 'll go . It 's my turn .
( Banging )
( Crickets chirping )
( Banging and clinking continue )
( Banging continues )
Who 's there ?
( Sighs )
( Door creaking )
( Creaking continues )
( Breathing heavily )
( Creaking and banging )
( Gasps )
( Door banging )
( Creaking and banging )
( Loud bang )
( Faint rattling )
( Door creaking )
( Wind whistling )
( Creaking continues )
( Smashing ) ( Gasps )
What are you doing here ?
Carlos ! Carlos !
What is it ?
Planning to bash the old lady 's head in ?
( Sniffs and sighs )
( Sighs )
( Shushing )
Sleep with sim n tonight .
If she shows up again , we 'll call the cops .
Sim n : mommy !
Mommy !
Can I wake up ?
Mommy ...
( Sighs )
Can I wake up ? Sim n , please .
You are already awake .
You can get up now , darling .
( Blinds opening )
( Door creaking )
( Door slams )
( Crickets chirping )
( Creaking )
( Thunder rumbling )
Wendy grew up
Wendy grows old and dies ?
Wendy grows old , but Peter Pan
takes her daughter to neverland every year .
Why doesn 't Wendy go too ?
Well ...
If Peter Pan came to get me , would you come too ?
No , I 'm too old to go to neverland , darling .
How old are you ? 37 .
At what age will you die ?
What sort of question is that ?
Not for a long time , until you 're very old .
I won 't grow old .
I 'm not going to grow up .
Will you be like Peter Pan ?
Like my new friends .
There 's more than one ? Six .
They won 't grow up either ? They can 't .
( Thunder rumbling )
( Thunder crashing )
What are they holding ?
Treasures . To play with .
I see . Your invisible friends play together ?
Sure .
They steal your treasure ...
Something you love , and you have to find it .
That 's the game ? Finding what they took from you ?
Yes , but following the clues .
If you find it , they Grant you a wish .
Well , now . And you have a treasure ?
Special coins .
An old man left them in the park . I think they 're gold ...
And very valuable .
Want to see them ?
( Heavy rain )
( Shushing )
Don 't look yet .
Laura : where 'd you get all this ? sim n : I found it .
What 's this ?
The first ice cream I had after my tonsil operation .
The special coins .
They 're not coins , they 're your baby teeth .
Where 'd you find them ? Can 't you see ?
They 're the first clue . They 've got my coins .
You want to play treasure hunt ?
( Sim n tuts ) the game 's started .
Remember where you kept my baby teeth .
If I find my treasure , I can make a wish .
Sand . Where do you find sand ?
You set this up , right ?
The beach ? No , no , it has to be at home .
( Thunder crashes )
( Shouts )
What 's this ?
The sewing box !
Sim n , wait !
Come on , hurry up !
This rings a bell .
I know , the key in the kitchen !
My treasure !
Those are daddy 's ...
I can make a wish ! I can make a wish !
I can make a wish ! Leave that alone !
I can make a wish ! ( Yells ) sim n !
Those are our things , you shouldn 't touch them .
Is that clear ? I didn 't . It was them !
Don 't lie to me . I 'm not lying .
You 're lying ! You say you 're my mother ...
And you 're not !
What ? You 're not my mother .
Who told you that ? My friend told me .
What friend ? Tom s .
Tom s told me the truth , that I 'm just like them ...
I have no mother or father ! And I 'm going to die !
You 're not my mother , you 're a liar !
( Door slams )
( Sighing )
We wanted you to be a bit older to talk about certain things .
If you want to ask us anything ...
Is Santa claus a lie too ?
Listen , sim n ...
You heard mommy and that lady talking ...
Saw the envelope and invented the game ...
Because you were afraid to ask about it .
What if I don 't take them ?
Nothing would happen .
If I don 't take them , how soon would I die ?
It would take many days , many weeks , even , right ?
Don 't worry , we 'll take care of you . You won 't get sick or die .
Carlos : ok ?
( Faint whispering )
( Whispering continues )
Child whispers : you don 't love me ! It 's a lie ! It 's a lie !
It 's a lie ! It 's a lie !
Laura : sim n , come down , son !
( Birdsong )
( Car horn honking )
Laura : sim n !
Sim n !
Hurry , the first kids are here ! Come on !
We can 't go yet . I want to show you something .
Really ? What is it ? Tom s ' little house .
Not now . Tomorrow , when we are alone .
No !
Not now , sim n . Now !
Go downstairs right now !
I don 't want to !
Go downstairs !
I said come and see Tom s ' house !
Ok , if you don 't want to go downstairs , don 't .
No one is forcing you .
Welcome
( laughter and chatter )
( Grunting )
( Fairground music playing )
( Clicking )
Where is the mask ?
( Children laughing )
( Children shouting )
( Children yelling )
Sim n ?
( Children laughing )
Sim n !
( Creaking )
Sim n ?
Darling !
Darling ?
Sim n !
( Whistle )
( Growling )
( Wheezing , grunting )
( Wheezing continues )
( Grunts )
( Floorboards creaking )
( Growling )
( Wheezing )
Sim n ?
Sim n , darling .
( Screeching )
( Screaming )
( Clattering )
( Gasps )
( Breathing heavily )
( Door creaking )
( Slams )
( Screeching )
( Gasping )
( Crying out )
( Yells ) Carlos !
( Banging )
( Creaking )
What 's going on ?
Darling !
Carlos : sim n ?
( Children laughing )
( Indistinct conversation )
Sim n !
( Loud clattering )
( Clattering and thumping )
( Conversation and laughter )
Sim n !
Sim n ! Simon !
( Yells ) sim n !
( Waves crashing )
Sim n !
Darling ! Sim n !
Laura !
( Shouting )
No !
Carlos : the tide is rising !
Sim n !
( Screaming )
Sim n ! Laura !
He 's over there , he 's over there , Carlos !
There 's no one , Laura ! Come on .
There 's no one ! We can 't stay here !
He 's there , Carlos !
( Sobbing )
( Splash )
( Water dripping )
Emergencies
( paper rustling )
Doctor : Carlos is here .
He spoke to the police ...
And now he wants to talk to you if you feel better .
( Baby crying )
How are you ?
He 's not in the cave .
But I saw someone , Carlos .
You must have imagined it in all the confusion .
Believe me , he wasn 't there .
I 'm Pilar .
I know it 's hard , but you must know we 're doing all we can ...
To locate your son as soon as possible .
Pilar is a psychologist .
She works with the police .
They 're working hard to find sim n .
I have a few questions .
Your husband told me about the adoption ...
And your son 's illness .
As he was adopted ...
There are possibilities we must consider .
What possibilities ?
He could have been kidnapped by a relative .
I heard you recently found ...
A woman intruder on the grounds .
Benigna escobedo , a social worker , came a few days ago .
We can 't find a social worker with that name .
Could you describe her ?
Mm ...
She was about 70 , with white hair ...
Pale eyes , very thick glasses .
Don 't worry , we will find her .
You can be sure of that .
( Police radio )
( Car door slams )
( Deep breathing )
( Both sigh )
How can they trust me with their kids after this ?
( Sighs deeply )
Let 's do something .
Wear my grandmother 's Saint Anthony medal ,
you know I 'm very fond of it .
To bring us good luck .
You don 't believe that .
Exactly . It will work if you have it .
But it 's not a present , I am lending it to you .
Give it back when we find sim n .
( Ragged breathing )
( Whistling )
( Door slams and creaks )
( Distant banging )
( Loud bang )
( Creaking and banging )
( Glass rattling , creaking above )
( Smashing and creaking continue )
Carlos !
( Crashing )
( Yells ) Carlos !
( Squeaks )
( Birds cawing )
( Creaking )
( Loud rumbling )
( Door slams )
Woman on radio : sim n s nchez 's parents ... Carlos : thank you .
.. Feel more and more forsaken .
The seven-year-old boy
disappeared from his home six months ago .
The situation is even more desperate ...
Because sim n is ill and needs daily medication . His parents ...
Laura : my son disappeared six months ago .
His name is sim n .
There are posters everywhere . You may have seen them .
We 've tried everything ...
But not one clue ...
Not even a trace .
My son had imaginary friends .
We never paid much attention ...
But I have the feeling they 're in the house .
Woman : I saw my daughter .
A year after her death .
It was at night , we were asleep .
I woke up ...
And without knowing why , I went to her room .
And there she was .
Smiling . Calm .
I think that was her way of telling me ...
" I 'm fine , I 'm safe . "
" Don 't suffer for me . "
It is not unusual to feel , in some way ...
The presence of a loved one after their death .
All of us in this bereavement group
could tell you similar stories .
You don 't understand .
My son is not dead .
His friends took him . I saw one of them
the same day he vanished .
He was at home .
I 'll do whatever it takes to recover my son .
I 'm not crazy ...
Believe me .
I know what I 'm saying .
Woman on radio : ... Cities on state of alert
due to gales , rain and snow .
The heaviest snowfalls will be recorded in the north .
Man on radio : north of asturias . Tonight , in some cities ...
20 cm of snow are expected
in the cantabrian mountains region ...
Cities that usually end up
isolated during these storms . And ...
( Music playing )
( Faint echoing laughter )
( Indicator ticking )
( Car horn honking )
( Brakes screeching )
It 's her .
The woman who came to the house .
Benigna ?
( Screaming )
( Screaming and shouting )
Sim n !
( Gasping )
Woman : he destroyed her . He destroyed her .
Second woman : she 's dead .
Pilar : we went to benigna 's house . We found some pictures ...
And old super-8 films .
I 'd like you to see them .
Are any of the faces familiar ?
Antonia , the principal ,
and these are the orphans . My friends .
This is mart n . She liked to be called mart n .
Rita .
V ctor ... I think his name was Guillermo .
That 's Alicia , she was blind .
And this is me .
Benigna ?
The woman that went to your house ...
Worked at the orphanage .
Laura : that 's impossible . I 'd remember .
Pilar : she wasn 't there very long .
She had a son . Tom s .
It seems that the child was born deformed ...
He was kept away from the others .
No one knew about him .
It was a total shock for the village
when they found the body .
What do you mean ?
It seems he disappeared while playing .
Child 's body found on beach
shortly after your adoption .
One of the orphans later confessed ...
That they had played a trick on him .
They went into the caves with Tom s ...
And took his mask off to see if he 'd come out .
But he never emerged . He drowned .
They found his body at low tide .
The children weren 't blamed . They were only playing .
That boy was in my house .
We asked everyone at the opening party .
No one remembers a child with a sack over his head .
( Ticking )
( Plays single note )
( Sobbing )
( Plays note )
( Ticking )
( Distant squeaking )
( Distant creaking )
( Creaking )
( Sighs )
I can 't remember what it 's like to sleep through the night .
I can 't stop thinking .
Remember what we called sim n when we met him ?
" Two little kilos " .
You used to say , " my two little extra kilos . "
That 's all he weighed .
The doctors said it wasn 't enough .
But it was plenty for us .
Although we knew that ...
There was little chance he could ever be normal .
But when we saw him ...
Saw his smile for the first time ...
His eyes , his bright eyes ...
Sim n made us strong , Carlos .
Together , we 're strong .
Together .
Forgive me if I get upset , but it 's hard .
Carlos , someone 's in the bathroom .
( Creaking )
Carlos : what is it ? Someone was here .
Carlos , don 't give me that look . Feel , it 's still warm .
Sure , I just got up .
Someone got into the bed .
I 'm convinced .
( Clock ticking )
Man : that 's what jung means when he says ...
It 's in the subconscious that
the living coexist with the dead .
The Germans have another name for " the herald of death " .
Doppelganger .
A being that appears in one 's own image .
A double .
To glance at him ...
Or at any of the others I 've shown you ...
Means , without the slightest doubt ...
A passport to the other world .
How long has your son been missing ?
Nine months .
Strange things are happening .
Things linked to his disappearance .
I don 't know who to turn to .
It 's not that simple .
You won 't find an exorcist in the yellow pages .
I tore it from my son 's kidnapper 's clothes .
The police say he 's been dead for over 30 years .
Someone has my son .
I don 't know why . But I won 't sit at home and wait .
Um ...
There 's someone in this field , someone I trust .
I 'm talking from the heart .
Would you allow a medium to visit your home ?
This wasn 't a children 's room in the orphanage , right ?
No , the bedroom was back there .
Then we should start here .
Enrique .
Perfect , give me an hour .
I want an old object from this house ...
Something related to its history , and , if possible ...
Some clothing from the past .
( Footsteps )
We 're not alone .
( Doorbell )
There 's a police psychologist , Pilar ...
Who would really like to attend the session .
If you don 't mind .
Perfect . Perfect .
Cops are cool !
( Whirring )
( Crackle )
Pilar : what does she need that doll for ?
Aurora needs an object to facilitate her trance .
Clothing and objects get her into it ...
And begin the regression .
Pilar : regression ? man : a psychic summoning .
Past , present and future are superimposed , and cross .
Like a sort of time travel .
Man : it may sound like witchcraft ...
But you mustn 't fear parallel perception .
If there 's anything , Aurora will see it .
If there 's anything , I hope we 'll all see it .
Man : everything 's ready , Enrique .
( Crackling )
Ready , whenever you want .
( Whirring )
( Creaking )
( Feedback whistling )
Aurora , can you hear me ? Perfectly . I 'm ready .
Man : here we go .
Man : everything around you is beginning to fade .
Darkness is forming a circle around you ...
It 's closing in on you .
Everything is fading . We 're no longer here .
Now you 're alone in the darkness ...
And the darkness begins to disappear .
I 'm going to count down ...
From ten ...
And once I 've finished ...
You can go wherever you want ...
And will be able to see ...
Anyone who is hiding in this house .
Ten ...
Nine ...
Eight ...
Seven ...
Six ...
Five ...
Four ...
Three ...
Two ...
One .
You can open your eyes .
( Inhales sharply )
Aurora : it 's cold ...
The window is open .
( Sighing )
( Shivering )
Aurora ...
I want you to look around you .
Is there anyone with you in the room ?
I can hear someone .
I can hear ...
( Footsteps thumping )
( Crackling )
I can hear something .
The sound comes and goes .
( Whirring )
I can 't hear it anymore .
I think I 've lost them .
I can hear something .
( Crackling , faint voices )
Child 's voice : all alone .
... all alone .
Aurora : children ...
I 'm sure it 's children .
At the end of the hall . I think it 's them .
( Feedback whistling )
( Crackling , faint voices )
( Radio static )
I can 't open it .
It 's closed .
( Crackling )
But there 's someone .
( Faint cries )
Why are you crying ?
Child : we 're sick ! Who 's sick ?
I won 't hurt you .
Don 't be afraid . Open the door .
( Faint shouts )
Don 't be afraid .
Open the door .
Child : we want you to open the door !
( Echoing voices )
( Distorted screams )
( Screams continue )
What have they done to you ?
( Crying and screaming )
What have they done ?
( Screaming continues )
Man : Aurora ...
Tell me what you see .
Five children .
They 're very sick . They 're crying .
What happened ?
( Crying and screaming )
They 're dying .
Who would want to poison you ?
( Screaming continues )
Child : someone 's going to kill us .
Someone 's going to kill us .
Is my son there ?
Aurora , is sim n with you ?
Is sim n here ?
( Distorted screams )
( Static )
( Crackling , indistinct noises )
( Faint voices , sobbing )
( Crackling drowns voices )
Man : Aurora ? Aurora , can you hear me ?
Let 's get her .
Aurora , stay in the middle of the room .
I 'll count from ten .
Ten ...
Nine ...
Eight ...
Seven ...
Six ...
Five ...
Four ...
Three ...
Two ...
One .
( Breathing heavily )
Aurora : I was in this house , but ...
Everything was different .
The beds , the toys , the d cor , everything was much older .
The light from the lighthouse came through the windows .
Are you sure you didn 't see sim n ?
It was too dark , I 'm sorry .
I couldn 't recognize anyone .
But the children were there .
You saw the children . Is that right ?
That 's right . You 're talking about ghosts .
Man : and what is a ghost , Carlos ?
There 's something here , and we all saw it .
When something terrible happens ...
Sometimes it leaves a trace ...
A wound that acts ...
As a knot between two time lines .
It 's like an echo ...
Repeated over and over , waiting to be heard .
Like a scar ...
Oh , I 'm sorry .
Like a scar or a pinch ...
That begs for a caress to relieve it .
Laura ...
We who are close to death ...
We are more receptive to these messages .
Hmm ?
You mean my son could see those children ...
Because ...
Well , Laura ... I think that 's enough .
Please take your things and leave .
Carlos , we can 't let them go like this .
Pilar : Laura , this is a farce ...
A sideshow trick .
I can 't believe this . Why ?
For what reason ? They 're right , aren 't they ?
They don 't want money . Not yet .
Laura : what should I do ?
Tell me , what should I do ?
It 's been a long time , and the police still haven 't found a single clue ...
Not a single clue ...
As to where my son can be , whether dead or alive .
What do I do , just sit and wait ?
Can it hurt to listen ?
Laura , stop ! No , you stop !
Tell me , Pilar ...
How many similar cases have you had in this damned village ?
Get another distraction , I didn 't invite you here .
( Engine starts )
What should I do ?
My dear ...
You are a good mother .
Your pain gives you strength , it will guide you .
But only you know how far you are willing to go ...
To find your son .
I don 't know what to do .
You hear , but don 't listen .
Seeing is not believing . It 's the other way around .
Believe ...
And you will see .
The search for sim n continues
What are you doing ?
We can 't stay here any longer .
We should go , at least for a while .
The children are here . Aurora saw them . I can 't leave .
You heard the voices .
Enrique was upstairs for one hour ,
playing around with the cables .
Can 't you see it could be a set-up ?
That 's Pilar 's theory , a set-up ?
Her rational theory ? Pilar is protecting us .
From what ?
Things like this evening .
People entering our home and fucking up our lives even more .
They just want to help . Help ?
Didn 't you hear them ?
Did they mention finding sim n ?
No . They just want to contact the dead , Laura .
If sim n 's alive , I can 't see how they can help us .
If he 's not , they won 't recover him .
I 'm neither willing nor able to keep taking this shit .
Please , Laura , let 's leave this house .
Carlos , you can 't ask me to give up . Neither you nor Pilar .
Laura , we can survive this .
Many couples lose a child and pull through .
I just want to be with sim n , don 't you understand ?
If you want to go , I can 't stop you .
I just want to see him , Carlos ...
That 's all I want !
( Bouncing sound )
( Creaking )
( Floorboards creaking )
( Loud creak )
Where are you ?
I 'm not afraid .
( Crashing , glass shattering )
( Bird cawing )
( Clattering )
( Breathing heavily )
You want to play ?
Are you playing with me ?
( Creaking )
( Squeaking )
( Distant squeaking )
( Squeaking continues )
( Doors slam )
( Creaking )
( Gasping )
( Bells chiming )
( Chiming continues )
( Clinking )
( Gasping )
( Creaking )
( Faint clattering )
Benigna ?
( Distant creaking )
( Coughs )
( Match striking )
( Rattling )
( Gasping )
( Breathing heavily )
( Gasping for breath )
God , don 't let it be him .
Please . Please , don 't let it be sim n . Please .
( Inaudible conversation )
There are five , right ? Carlos : yes .
All my friends .
Mart n , Rita , Alicia , Guillermo , v ctor .
Benigna killed them .
That 's why she went back to the shed , to recover their bodies .
I 've thought it out .
Their game killed Tom s ...
And now they 're playing with sim n and me , don 't you get it ? ( Film stops )
Sim n 's in danger and I don 't know how to play .
I don 't know how to play .
Laura , you 're making it up . Carlos , I saw it myself .
And this afternoon ? Who laid out the clues ?
Sim n made it all up to get your attention .
Who ?
Tell me ! Come on , who ?
I 've packed . I don 't want us to stay here .
I can 't leave yet .
I won 't live here ...
And you 're not staying alone .
I can 't just leave , there are too many memories , Carlos .
I have to say goodbye .
Two days .
Alone .
Please , I need this .
Please .
( Starts engine )
( Coughs )
( Hammering )
( Birds cawing )
( Thunder rumbling )
( Clatter )
( Bell ringing )
( Ringing continues )
( Whispers ) please bless what you have given us .
Thank you for letting us gather once again ...
And be together .
( Distant bells )
( Scraping )
What else do you want from me ?
What more must I do ? What more must I do ?
I have no time , I have no time .
I have no time , I have no time , I have no time .
( Sighs deeply )
You want to keep playing ? Is that it ?
Let 's make a deal . I 'll play a while ...
Then you tell me where sim n is , ok ?
Ok ?
( Yells ) ok ?
One , two , three , knock on the wall !
( Sobs ) one , two , three , knock on the wall .
( Bang ) one ...
One , two , three , knock on the wall .
One , two , three ...
( Pats )
Wait , wait , wait ! No .
Wait , I won 't hurt you . I just want to find sim n .
( Clattering )
( Door creaking )
( Door closes softly )
( Creaking )
( Door creaking )
( Creaking continues )
( Door slams )
( Banging )
( Banging continues )
( Bell chiming )
( Creaking and banging )
( Gasping )
( Banging )
( Clattering )
( Gasping )
( Breathing heavily )
( Creaking )
( Bell chiming )
( Clattering )
( Creaking )
( Crackling )
( Creaking continues )
Sim n ?
Mommy , why are you crying ?
Oh , my darling !
Are you ok ? You 're freezing .
Don 't worry about a thing .
( Thumping ) don 't be afraid , I 'll get you out .
( Clanging )
( Children laughing )
( Creaking )
Stay and play with us .
( Banging )
No , darling , we can 't stay to play .
( Children laughing )
( Banging and laughter continue )
( Gasping )
Listen to me , sim n .
Imagine it 's just you and me here . Ok ?
Think about before we came to this house .
Remember , darling ?
Think only about that , ok ?
Think only about that ...
Think about daddy ...
Think about next Christmas ...
And all the things we 'll do together .
So many things , darling !
Close your eyes . Close your eyes ,
tight , tight , tight , tight .
That 's it , really tight ...
And think about what you 'll be when you grow up .
( Children 's voices calling )
What would you like to be , darling ?
Think about the schools you 'll go to , the friends you 'll make .
( Thumping speeds up )
And just believe for a moment that ...
That Tom s and the other children aren 't real .
This is a fantasy , my darling ...
Like a nightmare .
( Pounding intensifies )
Do it for me , sim n , ok ?
When you open your eyes ...
Make them go away .
( Children laughing )
Please . Please , make them go away .
Please .
( Pounding stops )
( Exhales )
( Breathing heavily )
Close your eyes , darling ...
And keep on playing with me , ok ?
Keep on playing , darling , ok ?
( Coughs )
( Breathing heavily )
What is it ? Tom s ' little house .
( Clattering )
( Distant thumping )
( Crash )
( Flies buzzing )
Nooo !
No !
( Sobs )
Nooooo !
I found you . This isn 't fair .
I found you .
( Hums )
( Coughs )
( Clatter )
( Wind whistling )
( Creaking )
( Creaking continues )
( Banging )
( Creaking grows louder )
( Creaking continues )
I want sim n back .
( Creaking stops )
Mommy , mommy , can I wake up ?
Of course you can , darling . Of course you can .
Mommy , mommy ...
I found the special coins .
Now I just have to make a wish .
I wish you 'd stay and look after all of us .
( Door opens )
It 's Laura !
( Children laughing and chattering )
Laura !
She 's grown old , like Wendy in the story .
It 's Laura .
Laura .
Come , don 't be afraid .
The house . The beach . The lost children .
( Affirmative hum )
Once upon a time ...
There was a house near the beach ...
Where the lost children lived ...
( Continues telling story )
( Birds calling )
In memory of Laura and sim n ...
And of the orphans ...
Mart n , Rita , Guillermo , Alicia , v ctor , and Tom s .
( Squeaking )
( Sighs )
( Creaking )
The orphanage